<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>Rapid7 Vulnerability Exposure Alertse</title>
  <link>https://www.w3schools.com</link>
  <description>Important Information on Emergent Critical Vulnerabilities/Campaigns</description>
  <item>
    <title>F5 BIG-IP Multiple Remote Code Execution vulnerabilities</title>
    <link>https://data.labs.rapid7.com/vea/2021/2021/2021-03-19-F5-VEA.pdf</link>
    <description>
    <p>On March 10, 2021, F5 disclosed eight vulnerabilities, four of which are deemed "critical", the most severe of which is CVE-2021-22986, an unauthenticated remote code execution weakness that enables remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands on compromised BIG-IP devices.</p>
    <p>On March 18, 2021, NCC Group reported in-the-wild exploitation attempts and stated that they believe final development of a complete attack chain is imminent. Other cybersecurity experts agree, prompting the creation of this VEA.</p>
    </description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Multiple Microsoft Exchange zero-day vulnerabilities: HAFNIUM campaign</title>
    <link>https://data.labs.rapid7.com/vea/2021/2021-03-04-HAFNIUM-VEA.pdf</link>
    <description>
    <p>On March 2, 2021, the Microsoft Threat Intelligence Center (MSTIC) released details on an active
    state-sponsored threat campaign, which is leveraging four zero-day vulnerabilities to attack on-premise
    instances of Microsoft Exchange Server.</p>
    <p>In the attacks observed by Microsoft, the threat actor used the vulnerabilities to access on-premise
    Exchange servers, enabling them to access email accounts and allowing installation of additional
    malware to facilitate persistent access to victim environments. Microsoft Threat Intelligence Center
    (MSTIC) attributes this campaign with high confidence to HAFNIUM, a group assessed to be
    state-sponsored and operating out of China, based on observed victimology, tactics and procedures.</p>
</description>
  </item>
</channel>

</rss>
